http://www.feinviolins.com/privacy-policy

Online is the way to Save!Take 30% OFF orders $1500 & up-Use checkout code onlinesaveStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & CellosStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & CellosStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & CellosStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & Cellos1850 Grand Ave, St. Paul MN 55105 HomeViolinsViolasCellosBowsAPPRAISALSVintage ViolinsSmall SizesCases and AccessoriesShopBlogContact UsMeet the StaffFAQPrivacy PolicyRentalsFinancing- PayPal Credit360º View of the ShopGiftsInstrument Drop-OffAppointmentsMoreHomeViolinsViolasCellosBowsAPPRAISALSVintage ViolinsSmall SizesCases and AccessoriesShopBlogContact UsMeet the StaffFAQPrivacy PolicyRentalsFinancing- PayPal Credit360º View of the ShopGiftsInstrument Drop-OffAppointmentsStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & CellosStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & CellosStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & CellosStradivarius Model Violins, Violas & Cellos1850 Grand Ave, St. Paul MN 55105 HomeViolinsViolasCellosBowsAPPRAISALSVintage ViolinsSmall SizesCases and AccessoriesShopBlogContact UsMeet the StaffFAQPrivacy PolicyRentalsFinancing- PayPal Credit360º View of the ShopGiftsInstrument Drop-OffAppointments
Fein Violins Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWe take great care in making sure our customers' information is used only for the intent it was given to us. We do not share or sell private information such as phone numbers, emails, addresses, or names, with any entity EXCEPT with our credit card processor (PayPal), and with our shipping & mailing carriers/processors (UPS, USPS, and PirateShip.com). Payments are processed through PayPal to ensure the security of payments and personal information. Your credit card account (including your name, address, phone number, and email) WILL be entered into the PayPal system to process the charge. Except for ongoing Rental Agreements, Fein Violins does not store credit card information once the transaction has been completed.  Please note- For the protection of musicians everywhere, and ourselves, our Privacy Policy does not pertain to any illegal activity (such as theft, possession of or receiving stolen property, credit card fraud, or internet/wire fraud), stolen instruments, or reasonable suspicion of any illegal activity. We reserve the right and have the legal obligation to research an instrument's ownership, contact anyone we might consider being the rightful owner of an instrument, and/or law enforcement authorities in these situations. Nothing in our Privacy Policy supersedes any Federal, State, or Local law. Video Security- For security, your image and voice will be video recorded throughout the public areas of our business. These recordings will be held for a maximum of ten days unless there is any illegal activity or reasonable suspicion of any illegal activity. If any illegal activity has occurred or is suspected, the recordings will be turned over to the police.Shop
Copyright © 2018 Fein Violins, Ltd. - All Rights Reserved. Financing- PayPal Credit
